Together they will change the world.
Chloe and Theo is a comedy, drama film directed by Ezna Sands.
A young woman, Chloe, living by her wits on the streets of New York City, has a chance meeting with a wise Inuit Eskimo, Theo, who was sent to New
York by his elders to provide a message to the people of the world – We either change our destructive was or be destroyed by them.
Chloe, who has been searching for something to believe in, becomes inspired by Theo and , with the help of a kind lawyer, Monica,
the three of them present Theo’s story to the United Nations in hopes of creating a better future for all of us.
Chloe, played by Dakota Johnson.
Theo, played by Theo Ikummaq.
Tyler, played by Ashley Springer.
Mr. Sweet, played by André De Shields.
Monica, played by Mira Sorvino.
Narrator (voice), played by Michael Stiles.
Chloe and Theo is a 2015 American independent drama film written and directed by Ezna
Sands, and starring Dakota Johnson, Mira Sorvino, and Theo Ikummaq.
The film was released in the United States on September 4, 2015,
in a limited release, and through video on demand.
It received negative reviews and has 6% approval rating on Rotten Tomatoes.
This was the last film with Larry King as an actor
before his death in January 2021.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.